コードギアス反逆のルルーシュR2 TURN 19　裏切り
TURN 19　裏切り
We've confirmed a gigantic explosion
has occurred in the Tokyo settlement.
トウキョウ租界で巨大な爆発を確認しました
From the reports, we believe
it was a F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
報告にあったフレイア弾頭だと思われます
Is this correct, Your Majesty?
Should we be staying here at Kamine Island?
よろしいのですかこのカミネジマにとどまっていて
Enough! Let Schneizel handle it all.
よいシュナイゼルにすべて任せよ
一般市民の一次被害は 死者だけで1000万を超えているものと思われます
At least ten million of the general populace
are believed dead from the initial damage.
Secondary damages will result
in twenty-five million casualties.
二次被害による死傷者は推定でも2500万人
Since all rescue facilities were annihilated,
we have no way of rescuing any civilians.
救命施設も焼失したため 市民を救うてだてがありません
トウキョウ租界は 死にました
The Tokyo settlement has died.
No... How could this have happened?!
そんな こんなことって
They're all... They're all!
みんな  みんな
I... I did this?!
僕が やったのか
学園は無事か
The school's still all right.
But this is no longer a war.
でも これは もう戦じゃない
If they use this weapon again,
the Black Knights will be wiped out!
この兵器をもう一度つかわれたら 黒の騎士団は壊滅する
藤堂 私だ
Tohdoh... It's me.
Zero, we can't stay here...
ゼロここは
Have all forces land in the Tokyo
settlement. Search for Nunnally.
全軍 トウキョウ租界に降下しろ
ナナリーをさがすんだ
W-Wait! We've lost Asahina! And we
have massive casualties aside from...
ま 待て朝比奈がやられた
他にも多くの犠牲が
You think I care about that?!
知ったことかそんなもの！
Find Nunnally!
That takes top priority!
ナナリーをさがせ最優先だ
Have all of our forces
search for Nunnally!
全軍でナナリーを探し出すんだ！
What's happened to Zero?!
このゼロは
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
Kireigoto dake jaa ikirenai
Pretty words alone won't sustain you
Yasashisa dake jaa iyasenai
Kindness alone won't heal you
Ubawareta nowa nanda
What is it that was stolen from you
Kawaranai sekai de
In this unchanging world
Kikoetekita nowa nanda
What is it that you hear
Shikisai no uta
A song of color
Everything is bright...
Kudakechitta yume wo
Let our crumbled dreams resound
Asu no hate ni hibikaseru you ni
At the edge of tomorrow
Sekai no owari de
At the end of the world
Umareta hikari
The light that's born
Bokura hitotsu ni
Becomes one with us
Ima kaze no naka
Now blows in the wind
BETRAYAL
逃亡者は左滑走路なんだな
The fugitive's on the port side runway, right?
待ってくださいそれより軍の再編成を
Wait, please! We need to get
our forces reorganized first!
Understood!
I'll be back there in a minute!
わかっているすぐ戻るから
Ohgi!
扇
千草
Chigusa.
そこまでだ逃亡者くん
Hold it right there, Miss Fugitive.
コーネリア逃げ出したのはヴィレッタだと思ったが
Cornelia?! I thought it was
Villetta who had escaped.
久しいな節操無きテレビ屋が
It's been a long time.
The television man without a shred of honor...
ゼロのしわざか
Is Zero behind this?
Holding the princess captive?
皇女殿下を捕虜に？
He should have shown
a little more trust in me!
もう少し 私を信用してくれてもよいものを
足を狙え殺さずにとらえる
Aim for her legs!
I want her taken alive!
わかりました
Yes, sir!
当方はブリタニアの外交特使である
We are carrying a Britannian
special diplomatic envoy!
くりかえす当方は ブリタニアの外交特使である
I repeat, we are carrying a
Britannian special diplomatic envoy!
戦闘の意志はない
We have no intention of attacking!
外交特使？
A special envoy?
Minase! Was that plane cleared
to land through official channels?
水無瀬あの機体は正式なルートで申し込まれたのか
ん？
兄上！
Brother!
Impossible! He's personally
stepped right into the lion's den?
バカな！敵のまっただなかに
自ら乗り込んでくるとは
藤堂
Tohdoh! I told you to find Nunnally, didn't I?!
ナナリーをさがせといっているだろう
捜索部隊の指揮をとれ！
Now take command of the search team!
ち カレン きこえるか？
Kallen, do you hear me?
Rolo! Jeremiah!
ロロ！ジェレミア！
ナナリーは必ず生きている
Nunnally must still be alive!
Find her! Find Nunnally!
探せ！ナナリーを探し出すんだ！
全軍に告げる
Attention, all forces!
マクハリまで後退し 戦線をたてなおす
Fall back to Makuhari
and reform our battle line!
全軍至急後退せよ！
All forces, fall back immediately!
Tohdoh!
I told you to search for Nunnally...
藤堂！私はナナリーをさがせと
As long as big brother is safe...
兄さんさえ 無事なら
またの機会はある
...then we'll get another chance.
KAGOSHIMA SETTLEMENT COAST
どういうことだ？一時停戦とは
ブリタニアの思惑は？なぜビスマルクは兵をさげる？
What's the meaning of this temporary cease-fire?
What are the Britannians up to?!
Why did Bismarck withdraw his troops?!
We're still confirming that, but they
don't seem to want to attack us.
理由は確認中ですが 交戦の意志はないようです
それと トウキョウでも一時停戦したと
There seems to be
a cease-fire in Tokyo, as well.
ゼロの指示か
Did Zero order it?
ご主人さま あっ
Master?!
Hang in there, big brother.
兄さん しっかりして
ナナリーが
Where's Nunnally?
I'm here for you, big brother.
兄さんには 僕がいるよ
今までだって
We've been doing fine up till now
with just the two of us, haven't we?
僕ら二人だけでやってきたじゃないか
ジェレミアか 今は兄さんを静かにしてあげたいんだ
Jeremiah? I'd like big brother
to be left alone for now.
話ならあとで
You can talk to him later.
あっ そう あまり意味はないかもしれないけど
Right. It may not mean
much of anything.
兄さんには僕がついているから
Big brother has me
here with him, after all.
Why do you have this?!
どうしてお前がもっているんだ！
これはナナリーにあげるつもりだったんだよ！
I wanted to give this to Nunnally!
To Nunnally!
ナナリーに！
You think you can replace Nunnally
in my heart?! You damned imposter!
おまえなんかがナナリーのかわりになるもんか！
この偽物め！
まだ気づかないのか
Haven't you figured it out yet?
俺はお前が嫌いなんだよ
I hate you. I despise you!
大嫌いなんだよ！
何度も殺そうとして
I've tried over and over to kill you,
but I just keep missing the chance!
ただ殺し損ねただけだ！
にい さん
Big... brother?
出ていけ！
Get out of here!
I never want to see you again!
二度と俺の前に姿をみせるな！
出ていけ！
GET OUT OF HERE!!!
結局　わかっていなかったんです 私
In the end,
I just didn't understand.
どんな被害がおきるかなんて
Just how great the damage would be...
ニーナくん君はきめなくちゃいけない
Nina, you need to make a choice.
科学を捨てて心を守るか
Do you abandon science
to preserve your heart,
心を壊して科学に殉じるか
or destroy your heart and
sacrifice yourself to science?
そんなこと
How can I make that choice?
ロイド先生もえらんだんですか？
Did you make that choice too,
Prof. Lloyd?
My heart was destroyed from the very start.
僕はもとから壊れてるからね
それくらいの自覚はあるんだ
I'm self-aware enough
to acknowledge that.
I was the one who built F.L.E.I.J.A....
私が作ったフレイヤが
私が殺したんだ  みんな
I killed them... All of them!
All of them!
みんな
It's no use.
Zero won't answer.
ダメですゼロはでません
しかたないですね
We've no choice, then. We'll have to
meet with Schneizel without Zero.
シュナイゼルとの会談はゼロ抜きで
But Zero's our leader, isn't he?
でも うちのリーダーはゼロでしょう？
勝手にすすめちゃまずいんじゃな～い？
Won't it be wrong to proceed on our own?
虐殺です女子供も含めて全員殺すよう ゼロが指示をしたって
It was a massacre! They killed everyone,
including women and children!
All on Zero's orders, he said!
ディートハルト
Diethard! Why didn't you take
Schneizel captive immediately?
どうしてすぐにシュナイゼルをとらえなかった
護衛はナイトメア一騎だろう？
He only had one Knightmare guarding him, right?
We could have avenged Asahina...
朝比奈のかたきを
彼の専用機にフレイヤ弾頭がつまれています
His plane is equipped with
a F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
フレイヤ？
F.L.E.I.J.A.?
あの巨大爆発をひきおこした弾頭です
The bomb which caused
that gigantic explosion.
あそこで爆発すれば 私たちもゼロも無事ではすまかった
If it had exploded there,
neither we nor Zero would have survived.
シュナイゼルの目的はわからないが
We don't know what Schneizel's
objective here is.
とにかく 私たちだけでも話してみるしかないだろう
Our only option right now
is to talk to him.
私　パ～ス戻ってきた紅蓮をチェックしたいの
I'll pass. I'd like to check over
my Guren now that it's back.
では 交渉は 私 千葉 ディートハルト それに
Then the negotiators will be
myself, Chiba, Diethard, and...
Forget it.
I can't find Ohgi anywhere.
だ～めだみあたらねえよ 扇のやつ
ったくどこ行っちまったんだ
Jeez! Where'd that guy go?
カレン！
Kallen!
Thank goodness, you're back in one piece!
よかったなあ！無事で！
ごめんなさい心配かけて
Sorry to worry you all.
ねえゼロは？
Hey, where's Zero?
部屋にいるってさ
I heard he's in his quarters.
There's talk he's been wounded.
負傷したって話だけど
ナナリーさま生きていてください生きて
Lady Nunnally,
please be alive. Please!
おっ
以上が 私が嚮団で見聞きしたすべてです
That's all. Everything I saw
or heard at the Order.
ありがとう コーネリアこれで私は
Thank you, Cornelia.
With this, I can now...
お待たせしました
Forgive the wait.
悪ぃな～おまえらにやられた負傷兵の世話に手間取ってよ
Sorry. We've had our hands full with
all the casualties you guys caused.
玉城さん先ほども話したようにこの場は
Tamaki, we discussed this
already. You can't come in here.
俺は黒の騎士団内務掃拭賛助官だ
I'm the Black Knight's
Minister of Internal Janitorial Affairs.
I can be the representative for
General-Secretary Ohgi, right?
事務総長　扇要の代理でもあるだろ？
You're the only one
who has that impression.
それはあなたひとりの思いこみで
No, please. I'd like him to join
us in the conference, as well.
いや ぜひたちあっていただきたいのですが
はあ？
玉城真一郎
Shinichiro Tamaki.
ゼロの最も古い同志であり
As Zero's oldest comrade, I've heard you're
the brave veteran of many historic battles.
歴戦の勇士ときいています
Hah! The man talks sense.
へ！話せるじゃねえか！
T-Tamaki, please!
玉城さん
You rescued me
a long time ago, didn't you?
昔 私は君に助けられたことがあっただろう
その礼を伝えておきたかっただけだ
I only came here
to thank you for that.
しかし ふふっ
But still...
奇妙な関係だな私と君は
You and I share an odd
connection, don't we?
結局敵となる運命なのかもしれない
In the end, I suppose it's fate
that we be enemies.
ここで失礼する
I'll take my leave now, sir.
私はナナリー様をさがさねばならない
I must search for Lady Nunnally.
Nunnally is...
ナナリーは もう
生存者は順次名簿に登録するように
Survivors will please register
their names in order.
ＩＤ番号とは別に 名前 年齢 住所 血液型を申告
Along with your I.D. number, give your
name, age, address, and blood type.
治療が必要なものは医療受付にまわるように
If you require medical attention,
please go to the medical information desk.
できるだけ混乱を避けるため 落ち着いて冷静に行動を
To minimize any confusion,
please move in a calm and orderly manner.
Rivalz!
リヴァル！
Prez, you really are alive, aren't you?
会長！いきてたんですね～！！
うん生きてた生きてたよ
Yeah. I'm alive. I'm alive!
Oh, thank goodness!
よかったあ
You can say that again!
よかったねえ
I never settled my match
with Zero from before, did I?
ゼロとは 先日の勝負がついていませんでしたからね
ゼロはきませんお話の内容を確認したうえで
Zero isn't coming. Not until we determine
the details of what you wish to discuss.
でしょうねでてこられるはずがない
No, I wouldn't have
expected him to show up.
彼は人に相談するタイプではありません
He's not the type who consults
others about things.
ひとりで抱え込み 人を遠ざけるはず
I imagine he keeps things to himself
and holds people at a distance.
ゼロのこと よく知っておられるような口ぶりですね
You talk as if you know Zero intimately.
More than you people do.
あなたよりは
ゼロは 私やこのコーネリアの弟です
Zero is my and Cornelia's younger brother.
なんだとぉ？！
Say what?!
神聖ブリタニア王国　元第11皇子
The former 11th prince of
the Holy Britannian Empire:
ルルーシュ ヴィ ブリタニア
Lelouch vi Britannia.
私が最も愛し おそれた男です
The man I both loved and feared the most.
Impossible!
バカな
ゼロがブリタニアの皇子様だって？と玉城
You're sayin' Zero's a Britannian prince?!
ディートハルトお前は気付いていたのではないのか
Diethard, didn't you ever realize?
ジェレミアやヴィレッタから情報を手にいれていたようだしな
From the information you got
from Jeremiah and Villetta?
へ？
You're wasting your time.
無駄なことです
You can't cause chaos here by
spreading these absurd stories.
そのような戯言で我らを混乱させようなどと
我々は　ゼロを系譜ではなく
It's not Zero's lineage we acknowledge,
but rather the miracles he's performed for us.
起こした奇跡によって認めているのですから
But what if those miracles
were just shams?
しかし その奇跡が偽りだとしたらどうでしょう
Shams?
偽り？
ゼロには特別な力 ギアスがあります
Zero possesses a special power.
One known as Geass.
人に命令を強制する力です
The power to force anyone
to obey his orders.
強力な催眠術と考えてもらえば
You could think of it as
extremely powerful hypnosis.
奇跡のタネがその力だと
And you're saying his miracles
come from that power?
俺のゼロにケチつけてんじゃねえよ！
Don't you talk crap about my man Zero!
あいつはなあ頭がキレて 度胸があってすげえんだ！
He got brains and guts
and he's just awesome!
皇子とかギアスとかよぉ
All this talk about princes and Geass!
Where's your proof, huh? You got proof, huh?
証拠はあんのかよ証拠はああ？！
証拠ならある！
I've got your proof!
扇
Ohgi...
ヴィレッタまで
And Villetta?
彼のいったとおりだ
What he says is all true.
ゼロの正体はブリタニアの元皇子ルルーシュ
Zero's true identity is the former
Britannian prince Lelouch.
ギアスという力で人をあやつる
He controls people with that Geass
power of his. He's a con man!
ペテン師だ！
ゼロはずっと俺たちをだましていたんだ
Zero's been tricking us all along!
ずっと俺たちを駒として
Using us as pawns from the very start!
Ohgi, what are you saying?!
何いってんだよ 扇
しかし それが本当なら
But, if that's true, then...
だからといって
Then it doesn't matter!
これまでのゼロの実績が否定されるものではない
That doesn't repudiate all that
he's done for us up till now.
それに 本当にギアスがあるのなら
And if he really does have that
Geass power you speak of,
頼もしいじゃありませんか
then doesn't that just help us?
ブリタニアに対抗する強力な武器になる
It becomes a powerful weapon
to be used against Britannia.
その力が敵にだけ対して使われるものならばな
As long as he only uses it
against our enemies!
What?
何？！
まさか 私たちにも？
Are you saying he's used it on us?
そうだ
I am. He used it to control Euphemia,
his own sister!
やつは実の妹であるユーフェミアをあやつって
特区日本に集まったイレヴンを虐殺させた
He had her massacre the Elevens
gathered in the Special Zone!
Bullshit! Zero's a knight of Justice!
He'd never...
だぁほ！ゼロは正義の味方なんだよ！
そんなこと！
We have proof.
証拠ならあります
ルルーシュ 君がユフィにギアスをかけたのか？
Lelouch, did you use your
Geass on Euphy?
ああ
Yes.
日本人を虐殺しろと
You made her massacre the Japanese?
俺が命じた
I ordered her to.
では あの虐殺は
Then, that massacre was...
Zero did it! Not my little sister!
ゼロがやったことだわが妹ではない
ゼロが 日本人を殺せと？
You mean Zero...
He had the Japanese killed?!
偽物にきまってる！
It's gotta be a fake!
こちらが　ギアスをかけられた疑いのある事件 人物です
These are incidents and people which we
suspect were manipulated by his Geass power.
Kusakabe! Even Maj. General Katase!
あっ！　草壁 片瀬少将まで
そんな これは
I don't believe it. This is!
クロヴィス
Clovis...
私もかけられている
He used it on me, too.
これでガオハイの変わり身も
That explains Gao Hai's change of attitude.
ジェレミアたちが寝返ってきたことも
And completely explains why
Jeremiah and the others turned traitor.
すべて説明がつく
私とて　彼のギアスにあやつられていないという保証はない
There's no guarantee I'm not
controlled by his Geass as well.
そう考えると とても恐ろしい
When you think about it, it's terrifying.
まさか
You mean?!
Us, too?!
俺たちも
そしてもうひとつ
There's one more thing.
私たちは事前にフレイヤ弾頭のことをゼロに通告しました
We notified Zero about the F.L.E.I.J.A.
warhead before we used it.
無駄な争いを避けたかったからです
We wanted to avoid a useless battle.
ランスロットに通信記録が残っています
It's still in the Lancelot's
communications record. However...
しかし
我らに伝えなかった？
He never told us.
We can't trust Zero!
ゼロは信用できません
省悟
Shougo...
I wanted to believe in him!
I wanted to!
俺は 彼を信じたかった
信じていたかった
But to him, we're nothing but...
Nothing but pawns?! Dammit!
でも 俺たちは彼にとって  ただの
駒だってのか！
チクショウ！ゼロのやろう！よくも！
How could he do this to us?!
チクショウーー！！
DAMMIT!!!
皆さん 私の弟を
Everyone... My brother...
Will you hand Zero over to me?
ゼロをひきわたしていただけますか
条件があります
On one condition!
扇
Ohgi!
You think you're in any
position to bargain?!
取引できる状況だとおもっているのか？
ききましょう
Let's hear it.
日本を　返せ
Japan... Give it back!
信じた仲間を裏切るんだ
I'm about to betray someone I trusted.
せめて日本くらい取り返さなくては
If I don't at least get Japan back,
then I'll never forgive myself!
俺は自分を許せない
Master, please take off your clothes.
ご主人さま 服をぬいでください
えっ？
What?
どこか痛いんですか？
Do you hurt anywhere?
手の届かない所なら 私が
If it's someplace
you can't reach, I can...
ああそうだな
That's right...
It's someplace I can't reach.
手のとどかないところか
ゼロはいってもよろしいでしょうか
Zero, may I come in?
私です
It's me.
カレン
Kallen.
扇さんが4号倉庫にきてほしいって
Ohgi said he wanted you
to come to storeroom four.
４号？
Four?
細かいことは私も
Sorry, but I didn't ask
why he wanted you.
ご主人さま
Master?
服を脱いでください　私　がんばってみますから
Please take off your clothes.
I'll do my best, I promise.
はあ？
何やってたのよ？あんたたちは！
What the hell have you two been up to?!
While I've been rotting in a cell, you've!
私がつかまってる間に
No, you've got it wrong.
C.C. is now... Um...
ち ちがうこのC.C.はその
記憶を失っているんだ
She's lost her memory.
えっ？
俺のせいで
It's my fault.
だからお前が知っているC.C.はもういないんだ
So, the C.C. you knew... is gone now.
C.C.が いない
C.C.'s gone?
C.C.がいない
C.C.'s gone.
And now Nunnally's been killed.
ナナリーもいなくなった
じゃあルルーシュは？
That means Lelouch is...
カレン
Kallen.
よく無事でいてくれたな
It's good you made it back.
I'm sorry it took so long to send help.
救助が遅くなってすまなかった
ルルーシュ
Lelouch... I happened to talk to Nunnally.
She saved me.
私ね ナナリーと話したわ
私のこと 助けてくれたの
I see.
そうか
Look... I'm not sure what
to say at a time like this,
あの こんなときにいうのもなんだけど
but when I lost my brother, l...
私もお兄ちゃんがいるから うっ
観念しろ　ゼロ！
Surrender quietly, Zero!
よくも我々をペテンにかけてくれたな
How dare you con us like you have!
君のギアスのことはわかっているんだ
We know all about your Geass power!
伝説の英雄ゼロは 志なかばにして戦死
The legendary hero Zero died in
battle before realizing his ambitions.
しかしその勇敢なる生きざまは永遠に語り継がれることでしょう
But his gallant life will live on in legend!
Is that the script you've
written for me, Diethard?
ディートハルト
それがおまえの台本か？
本当なら あなたがブリタニアに勝利するところまで撮りたかったのですが
To be honest, I wanted to film
your triumph against Britannia,
but I'm afraid that show
has been canceled.
残念ながら　番組は打ち切りです
どうする？ナイトメアが邪魔だが
What do I do? The Knightmares are in the way,
but Ohgi and the others are defenseless!
扇たちは無防備だ
バレないようにギアスをつかえば
If I can use my Geass
without them noticing!
みんなお前を信じていたのに！
Everyone trusted you!
井上も吉田も　お前のために死んだんだ！
Inoue and Yoshida even died for you!
待って！一方的すぎるわ こんなの！
Wait a minute!
This is way too one-sided!
ゼロのおかげで私たちここまで来られたんじゃない?
Look how far we've been able to come
because of Zero! Let him have his say...
彼の言い分も
Step aside, Kallen!
どけ！カレン！
ゼロと一緒に死にたいのか？！
Do you want to die with Zero?!
Don't tell me he used
his Geass on you, too!
まさかギアスにかかっているんじゃないよな？
Answer me, Lelouch.
What am I to you?
答えて　ルルーシュ
あなたにとって　私は何？
私あなたとなら
If I could stay with you,
I would... Please.
ねえ
そうかこれはあなたのチェックか
I see.
This is you calling "check" on me.
ならば　万が一にも隙はないのでしょう
Then there must not be
any way out of this for me.
ねえ お願い！答えて！
Please, just answer me!
フハハハハっ！
バカが！今頃気づいたのか
Fools! You finally figured it out!
自分たちが利用されていることに
That I've been using you all.
貴様らが 駒にすぎないということに
That you're nothing but pawns to me!
Zero! So, you really are...
ゼロ 君はやはり
Zero!
ゼロ～～！
ルルーシュ
Lelouch...
カレン
Kallen, you were the most
special piece of all for me to play.
君はこの中でも特別優秀な駒だった
そう すべては盤上のこと
That's right. This was all just
a board for me to play on.
Just a game to me.
ゲームだったんだよ これは
そう
I see...
さよなら ルルーシュ
Goodbye then, Lelouch.
構えー！
Take aim!
カレン  君は生きろ
Kallen... You have to live.
撃てー！
Fire!
Are you okay, big brother?!
大丈夫？兄さん
ロロ！
Rolo!
Never mind!
Open fire on the Shinkirō, too!
かまわん蜃気楼ごと撃てー！
待って！
Wait!
Big brother, I'll protect you!
兄さんは 僕が守る！
やめろ！ロロ！もういんいんだ！
Stop it, Rolo! That's enough!
あっ 御主人さま
Master...
あっ消え蜃気楼が
They're gone!
The Shinkirō!
Like at Babel Tower...
バベルタワーのときの
アーニャゼロは逃げたわ
Anya, Zero's escaped.
Can you capture him with the Mordred?
モルドレッドでつかまえられる？
破壊 なら
If I can destroy him...
I never realized how difficult it was to
calculate the Absolute Defense Field.
絶対守護領域の計算が
こんなにたいへんだなんて
ふふっやっぱりすごいや僕の兄さんは
My big brother really is
incredible, isn't he?
Rolo! I have no reason
to live any longer!
ロロ！俺はもう生きる理由なんて
はっ何？この動き
How can it move like that?
I won't let them kill you!
I swear!
殺させない絶対に！
こんな広範囲でギアスを！
Using your Geass over
such a large area...
ロロ これ以上はおまえの心臓がもたない
Rolo, your heart won't be able
to take the strain!
Attention, all units!
The Shinkirō has been stolen!
各員につぐ蜃気楼が奪取された
Any units capable of combat,
destroy the Shinkirō!
攻撃可能な部隊は 蜃気楼を破壊せよ
I repeat, destroy the Shinkirō!
繰り返す蜃気楼を破壊せよ！
Enough, Rolo!
I don't want to live any more!
もういいんだ ロロ
俺はもう
ダメだよ 兄さん だって
I won't, big brother. Because...
やめ
Stop...
僕はずっと　誰かの道具だった
For my entire life,
someone has always been using me.
...doing this, Rolo!
Why are you trying to...
（や）めるんだ！ロロ!どうして俺なんかを
僕は嚮団の道具だった
I was used by the Order...
（た）すけるんだ？！俺は
...to save me?! I...
And then you used me, big brother.
その次は　兄さんの
Yeah... Maybe you've just
been using me all this time...
たしかに僕は　兄さんに使われていただけかもしれない
But only the time
I spent with you was real.
でも　あの時間だけは　本物だった！
...was only...
おまえのことを ！
Thanks to those memories...
あの想い出のおかげで
ようやく僕は　人間になれた！
They finally made me...
human!
利用して ！　ロロ！
...using you! Rolo!
だから　もう
That's why... I'm not...
僕は
I'm not!
やめてくれ！
Stop it! Don't use your Geass!
Do you want to die?!
ギアスをつかうな！
死にたいのか？！
I... am not... a tool!
僕は 道具じゃない
これは 僕の意志なんだから！！
I do this... of my own... free will!
ロロ　どうして俺を助けた？
Rolo, why did you save me?
俺は おまえを
After all I've done to you?
兄さんは　うそつきだから
Because you're a liar, big brother.
えっ？
It was a lie, wasn't it?
About trying to kill me...
嘘だよ ね？
僕をころそうとしたなんて
About... hating me...
僕がきらい なんて
Yeah. You saw right through it,
didn't you?
そうかすっかり見抜かれているな
さすがは俺の弟だ
Just what I'd expect
of my little brother.
そう だよ
Yeah... That's right...
僕は 兄さんのことなら
Because... I know...
なんでも わかるん だ
everything about you... big brother...
Yeah. You did.
ああそうだよ
お前の兄は　うそつきなんだ
Your big brother... is nothing but a liar.
対象を確認できません
We cannot confirm the target.
Increasing the search area.
捜索範囲を広げます
Could you send in ground units, please?
地上班をよこしてください
ナナリー　ロロ　シャーリー　黒の騎士団
Nunnally... Rolo... Shirley...
The Black Knights...
俺はすべてを失った
I've lost everything.
これが残された結果
This is the result
which I've been left with.
いや　報いか
No. It's the punishment I deserve.
But now, thanks to this...
でも　だからこそ
ありがとう　ロロ
Thank you, Rolo.
お前がつないだこの命
You saved my life because there's
still a task for me to do, didn't you?
俺にはまだ
成さねばならないことがあったんだよな
そう俺には
Yes. Something for me to do...
まさか
Who would have imagined?
ここのシステムを使うことになろうとはな
That I would ever use the system here?
ラグナレクの接続
The Ragnarok Connection.
これで古い世界は破壊され新しい世界は創造される！
Now the old world shall be destroyed,
and a new world created in its place!
わが父　シャルル ジ ブリタニアよ
Charles zi Britannia, my father!
俺の地獄への道行きには
If I am on the road to hell,
おまえもいっしょにきてもらう
then I'll drag you down there with me!
I swear it!
それが  ！
Dakuse wa oni
This corrupt world is filled with demons
Seigi wa nanzo to
What is justice?
Tou mae ni aragae yo
Resist, don't just question
Akutoku no hana
The flower of evil
Gizen no yume
Dreams of hypocrisy
Mishi me niwa me wo sashi
Give your gaze to the eyes that see them
Sei mo ja mo wakatareru koto nashi
The line between right and wrong cannot be known
Hikari wa tae taiji no you ni
Light is gone, and you slumber
Kimi wa nemuru yami no shikyuu
Like an unborn child in the womb of darkness
Kodoku koso itooshii
Isolation is what you love
Yui-itsu no mikata to naru darou
It will probably be your only ally
Hitori hitori chishio ni mamire
One by one, stained with the tide of blood
Kono jidai ni umare ochita
You were born into this era
Erabareshi oujira yo
Oh, chosen princes
Tatakai koso shukuen
Battle shall be your banquet
Aa ware wa uruwashii zenchi
Oh, I am graceful omniscience
Ai no haha
The loving mother
Kimi wo umu
Who bore you
Kono chichi ni hagukumishi mono wa
The ones who were raised on my breast
Jigoku no harakara
Are your brethren in hell
Mokushi no in
The mark of apocalypse
Shinri wa nanzo to
What is truth
Shirimosezu uzumoreshi intoku no tane
A seed of secrecy buried where no one knows
Moroha no ken
A double-edged sword
Nuku ha niwa ha wo muke
Turn its blade upon the unsheathed blade
Mamorubeki mono dake wo shinjite
Believe only in what you must protect
Aru ga mama ni kimi wa
And in your own way
Kimi wo hanate
You'll set yourself free
ロロ　俺とお前の関係なんだったんだろな
Rolo... What was our relationship,
in the end?
俺はいつも後になって気が付くんだ
お前はルルーシュ　ヴィ　ブリタニアではなく
It's strange to think.
Even knowing the truth, you still...
ルルーシュ　ランペルージの弟なんだって
なあ
You of all people stuck
by me to the very end.
ルルーシュだ　今週も楽しんでくれてありがとう
Yeah...
いつも応援してくれるみんなにご覧のプレゼントを送る
I always realize these things
after it's too late.
To you, I wasn't
Lelouch vi Britannia, was I?
パスーワードを入力して　こちらのケータイサイトから応募してほしい
You were Lelouch Lamperouge's
little brother.
今から一時間限定の受付だ
EMPEROR DISMISSED
もちろん　特製の待受けもあるぞ
それでは諸君　来週のお楽しみに